http://www.southernwinegroup.com/privacy

Cart
A PIONEERING U.S. NATIONAL WINE IMPORTER AND WINE PRODUCER FOR TWO DECADES
Privacy Policy
Elixir Wine Group, LLC is committed to protecting your privacy. We only use the information we collect about you to process orders and to provide support and upgrades for our products. Please read on for details about our privacy policy.What information do we collect? How do we use it?When you order, we need to know your name, e-mail address, mailing address, credit card number, and expiration date. This allows us to process and fulfill your order and to notify you of your order status.Of Legal Age Requirement:By the use of this site you confirm that you are at least 21 years of age and are authorized to shop and make alcoholic beverage purchases online and to receive packages of alcoholic beverages at the home or business address you supply.How does Elixir Wine Group protect customer information?We use a Secure Server for collecting personal and credit card information. The secure server layer (SSL) encrypts (scrambles) all of the information you enter before it is transmitted over the internet and sent to us. Furthermore, all of the customer data we collect is protected against unauthorized access.What about “cookies”?“Cookies” are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive. Our online store uses cookies for retaining user name and passwords for your browser.Will Elixir Wine Group disclose the information it collects to outside parties?Elixir Wine Group LLC does not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others.Elixir Wine Group LLC may release account information when we believe, in good faith, that such release is reasonably necessary to (i) comply with law, (ii) enforce or apply the terms of any of our user agreements or (iii) protect the rights, property or safety of Elixir Wine Group, our users, or others.In Summary:Elixir Wine Group LLC is committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect on the site to make shopping at Elixir Wine Group as simple as possible and to enhance your overall shopping experience. We do not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others.Your Consent:By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by Elixir Wine Group LLC. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.Elixir Wine Group LLC also provides links to affiliated sites. The privacy policies of these linked sites are the responsibility of the linked site and Elixir Wine Group LLC has no control or influence over their policies. Please check the policies of each site you visit for specific information. Elixir Wine Group cannot be held liable for damage or misdoings of other sites linked or otherwise.Questions and Feedback:If you have any questions or feedback related to our Privacy Policy, please email us at info@elixirwinegroup.com or use the contact page on this site.Thank you for shopping at Elixir Wine Group LLC!
Facebook
Twitter
Youtube
Instagram
About
Our Wines
Contact
Trade
Cart
©2020 Elixir Wine Group, LLC. All rights reserved.  |  11 NW Lava Rd., Bend Oregon 97703  |  T 541 388 5330  |  info@elixirwinegroup.com  |  Privacy Policy  |  Newsletter Sign-Up
The Company does not sell or serve alcohol to persons under the age of 21. By accessing the Site, you affirm to be of legal drinking age.
Scroll to Top
